Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
- NATCA (National Air Traffic Controllers Association), Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: Hot Mike - the grass toots voice of the NATCA membership -- Winter 1990, Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: NATCA newsletter -- vol. 5, no. 2 (Mar. 1991), Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: So they said 'it would never happen', Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 24: Testimony of the NATCA on HR 4003, Controller re-hire legislation, 1986; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 25: Statement for the hearing record of NATCA before the House Post Office & Civil Service, 1990; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 26: Testimony of R. Steve Bell, Pres., NATCA, before the House Science, Space & Technology Subcommittee on Transportation on HR 4950.., 1990; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 27: Statement of R. Steve Bell, Pres., NATCA, before the House Public Works & Transportation Subcommittee on Aviation, 1991; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 28: Testimony of John F. Thornton, Senior Director, Legislative Affairs, NATCA before the House, 1990; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
    Author: John F. Thornton
  - Item 29: Prepared remarks of R. Steve Bell, Pres., NATCA, before the 10th Convention of the Professional Airways System Specialists, 1989; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 30: Testimony of R. Steve Bell, Pres., NATCA, before the House Appropriations Subcommittee on Transportation on the FAA's FY 1990, 1989; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 31: Testimony of John F. Thornton, Senior Director, Legislative Affairs, NATCA before the House, 1988; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 32: Prepared remarks of R. Steve Bell, Pres., NATCA, before the Pilot/Controller Communications Awareness initiative press conference, 1988; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 33: Remarks of John F. Thornton, National Coordinator, NATCA, before the Air Line Pilots Assoc. Annual Safety Forum, 1987; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 34: Testimony of John F. Thornton, Senior Director, Legislative Affairs, NATCA before the Senate Commerce, Science and Trans, 1987; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 35: Testimony of the NATCA before the Senate Commerce, Science and Transportation, 1987; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 36: Testimony of Joseph M. Bellino, Representative, NATCA, 1987; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
    Author: Joseph M. Bellino
  - Item 37: Testimony of the NATCA, before the Senate Commerce, Science & Transportation Subcommittee on Aviation on S.2417, 1986; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 38: Testimony of the NATCA, before the Joint Economic Subcommittee on Investment Jobs, and Prices on Aviation Safety, 1986; Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 39: Isn't it time that you became involved in the political process?, Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 40: What is NATCA?, Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 41: Benefits: for NATCA members, Associate Members, Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 42: NATCA, Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - Item 43: How your NATCA dues dollar is spent, Publication (Box 494, Folder 5)
- NATCA (National Air Traffic Controllers Association), Publication (Box 495, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the National Air Traffic Controllers Association. MEBA/AFL-CIO and the Federal Aviation Administration, Department of Transportation: August 1993, Publication (Box 495, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Agreement between the National Air Traffic Controllers Association. MEBA/AFL-CIO and the Federal Aviation Administration, Department of Transportation: August 1993, Publication (Box 495, Folder 1)
- NATCA (National Air Traffic Controllers Association), Publication (Box 495, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the National Air Traffic Controllers Association. MEBA/AFL-CIO and the Federal Aviation Administration, Department of Transportation: Effective May 1989, Publication (Box 495, Folder 2)
- Alaska, Publication (Box 495, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the State of Alaska and the Centralized Correspondence Study Education Association covering Advisory Teachers: January 1, 1984 - December 31, 1986, Publication (Box 495, Folder 3)
- Alaska. Confidential Employees Association, Publication (Box 495, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agreement - 1987-1989 (Box 495, Folder 4)
- Alaska, Publication (Box 495, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Penciled in title - Labor Trades and Crafts, 1989; Publication (Box 495, Folder 5)
- APEA (Alaska Public Employees Association), Publication (Box 495, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: advertisement - Public Employees: Alaskans working for Alaska's future, Publication (Box 495, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Letter of undertanding between the State of Alaska and Alaska Public Employees Assoc., 1989; Publication (Box 495, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: By-laws and articles of incorporation, 1984; Publication (Box 495, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Agreement City of Nome and Alaska Public Employees Assoc., 1984-1987 (Box 495, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Agreement between the State of Alaska and the Alaska Public Employees Association, Supervisory Unit: January 1, 1987 to December 31, 1989, 1987-1989 (Box 495, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Agreement between State of Alaska and the Alaska Public Employees Association covering General Government Unit Employees: 1980-1982, Publication (Box 495, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Agreement between State of Alaska and the Alaska Public Employees Association covering Supervisory Unit Employees: 1984-1986, Publication (Box 495, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Agreement between State of Alaska and the Alaska Public Employees Association covering General Government Unit Employees: 1984-1986, Publication (Box 495, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Agreement between State of Alaska and the Alaska Public Employees Association covering General Government Unit Employees: 1984-1986, Publication (Box 495, Folder 6)
- APEA (Alaska Public Employees Association), Publication (Box 495, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: EPIC (Employees Political Information Committee) - Constitution and by-laws - Rev. May 1984, Publication (Box 495, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Agreement between the State of Alaska and the Alaska Public Employees Association: January 1, 1987 to December 31, 1989, 1984; Publication (Box 495, Folder 7)
- APEA (Alaska Public Employees Association), Publication (Box 495, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the State of Alaska and the Public Safety Employees Association: January 1, 1987 to December 31, 1989, Publication (Box 495, Folder 8)
- APEA (Alaska Public Employees Association), Publication (Box 495, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Negotiated agreement between the Alaska State Board of Education and Teachers Education Association of Mt. Edgecumbe (T.E.A.M.E.): July 1, 1988 - June 30, 1991, Publication (Box 495, Folder 9)
- APEA (Alaska Public Employees Association), Publication (Box 495, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the State of Alaska and Alaska Tri Trades Public Service Council covering Labor Trades and Crafts Unit Employees: 1974, Publication (Box 495, Folder 10)
- Aluminum, Brick and Glass Workers International Union, Publication (Box 495, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Memorandum of agreement on Pension agreement modification, 1985; Publication (Box 495, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: 1982 Amendment to 1980 agreement between LOF Glass and, Publication (Box 495, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Agreement and working rules between Aluminum Company of America and Aluminum, Brick, and Glass Workers International Union - AFL-CIO: Local Nos. 105, 115, 415, 445, 420, 104, 1986; Publication (Box 495, Folder 11)
- Aluminum, Brick and Glass Workers International Union, Publication (Box 495, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1989; Publication (Box 495, Folder 12)
    Notes: Photocopy of constitution adopted at Convention (July 31-Aug. 4, 1989)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1993; Publication (Box 495, Folder 12)
- Aluminum, Brick and Glass Workers International Union, Publication (Box 496, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Financial statements, 1987; Publication (Box 496, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Financial statements, 1987; Publication (Box 496, Folder 1)
- Aluminum, Brick and Glass Workers International Union, Publication (Box 496, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Political action handbook, Publication (Box 496, Folder 2)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 496, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Air Line Pilots Assoc. information, Publication (Box 496, Folder 3)
- American Trade Union Delegation, Publication (Box 496, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: U.S. labor looks at Europe, 1951; Publication (Box 496, Folder 4)
- International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers Local No. 12, Publication (Box 496, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Agreement of working conditions between the Insulators Contractors Association of NYC, 1972; Publication (Box 496, Folder 5)
- International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Publication (Box 496, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws (Philadelphia, PA) - 1987, Publication (Box 496, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Constitution and By-Laws (Philadelphia, PA) - 1987, Publication (Box 496, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Constitution and By-Laws (Toronto, Canada) - 1992, Publication (Box 496, Folder 6)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 496, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Agreement between American Motors Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW): Locals 72 and 75: July 8, 1985 through September 16, 1988, Publication (Box 496, Folder 7)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 496, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Agreement between American Motors Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW) and its Locals 72 and 75: September 17, 1980 through September 16, 1983, Publication (Box 496, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Agreement between American Motors Corporation, Kenosha Plant, Kenosha, Wisconsin and the International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America UAW: Locals 72: July 8, 1985 through September 16, 1988, Publication (Box 496, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Agreement between American Motors Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW) and its Locals 72 and 75: Employee investment plan and applicable amendments to September 17, 1980, Publication (Box 496, Folder 8)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 496, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Settlement proposal - Boston University to District 65, UAW, 1994; Publication (Box 496, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Collective bargaining agreement by and between Brunner Engineering & Mfg., Inc. and the International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and its U.A.W. Local Union No. 2158, Bedford, Indiana, 1982; Publication (Box 496, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Agreement Trustees of Boston University and District 65 United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1988; Publication (Box 496, Folder 9)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 496, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW: October 25, 1979: incorporating January 5, 1980, Special Provisions, Production and Maintenance, Publication (Box 496, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW: includes only Amendments of December 10, 1982 to the October 25, 1979 Agreement and Amendments thereto: Production and Maintenance, Publication (Box 496, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW: October 28, 1985: Production and Maintenance, Publication (Box 496, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW: includes only Amendments of December 10, 1982 to the October 25, 1979 Agreement and Amendments thereto: Parts Depot, Publication (Box 496, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW: includes only Amendments of December 10, 1982 to the October 25, 1979 Agreement and Amendments thereto: Office and Clerical, Publication (Box 496, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Letters, Memoranda and agreements: 1982 Production and Maintenance Agreement between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW: includes only Amendments of December 10, 1982 to the October 25, 1979 Agreement and Amendments thereto, Publication (Box 496, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: 1985 Pension Agreement between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW: Production and Maintenance, Parts Depots, Office and Clerical, Engineering, Publication (Box 496, Folder 10)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 497, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Summary of agreement between UAW Service/Maintenance Unit & Cornell University, Publication (Box 497, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: UAW-Caterpillar Contract - Major improvements and changes -- 1973-1976 (Box 497, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: 1988-1992 agreement between Cornell University and Cornell Service and Maintenance Unit, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 2300., Publication (Box 497, Folder 1)
    Author: Cornell Service and Maintenance Unit
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 497, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Exhibits to the Production & Maintenance, Parts Depot, Office & Clerical and Engineering agreements of November 19, 1990 between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 497, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Exhibits to the Production & Maintenance and Parts Depot agreements of October 28, 1985 and Office and Clerical and Engineering agreements of between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 497, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 497, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Agreements between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW: November 19, 1990: Engineering, Office & Clerical, Publication (Box 497, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Letters, Memoranda and Agreements: 1990 Production and Maintenance Agreement between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 497, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW: November 19, 1990: Production and Maintenance, Publication (Box 497, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: 1990 Pension Agreement between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW: November 19, 1990: Production and Maintenance, Parts Depot, Office and Clerical, Engineering, Publication (Box 497, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 497, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 1981-1983 agreement between Cornell University and Cornell Service and Maintenance Unit, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America., Publication (Box 497, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: 1981-1983 agreement between Cornell University and Cornell Service and Maintenance Unit, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America., Publication (Box 497, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: 1985-1988 agreement between Cornell University and Cornell Service and Maintenance Unit, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 2300, Publication (Box 497, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: 1985-1988 agreement between Cornell University and Cornell Service and Maintenance Unit, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 2300, Publication (Box 497, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: 1983-1985 agreement between Cornell University and Cornell Service and Maintenance Unit, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 2300, Publication (Box 497, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: 1983-1985 agreement between Cornell University and Cornell Service and Maintenance Unit, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 2300, Publication (Box 497, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Agreement between ConDiesel Mobile Equipment Division, Condec Corporation and Local 259, UAW: 1982-1984, Publication (Box 497, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Agreement between ConDiesel Mobile Equipment Division, Condec Corporation and Local 259, UAW: 1982-1984, Publication (Box 497, Folder 4)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 498, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Benefits Plans and Agreements -- UAW and the Ford Motor Company -- (Part II only), 1990; Publication (Box 498, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Benefits Plans and Agreements -- UAW and the Ford Motor Company -- (Part II only), 1990; Publication (Box 498, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Benefits Plans and Agreements -- UAW and the Ford Motor Company -- (Part II & III only), 1984; Publication (Box 498, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Agreements between Ford Motor Co. and UAW -- (Part I only), 1984; Publication (Box 498, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 498, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreements between UAW and the Ford Motor Co. (Vol. I only), 1990; Publication (Box 498, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Agreements between UAW and the Ford Motor Co. (Vol. I only), 1990; Publication (Box 498, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Letters of understanding between UAW and the Ford Motor Company (Vol. IV only), 1990; Publication (Box 498, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Letters of understanding between UAW and the Ford Motor Company (Vol. IV only), 1990; Publication (Box 498, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 498, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Letters of understanding between UAW and the Ford Motor Company (Vol. IV only) -- photocopy, 1987; Publication (Box 498, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: 1987 Ford-UAW National Agreements -- Highlights, Publication (Box 498, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 498, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Benefits Plans Deere & Co. and the UAW, 1994; Publication (Box 498, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Mack Avenue Engine Plant I Local Agreement between Daimler Chrysler Corp. and Local 51 UAW, 1999; Publication (Box 498, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Contract between GTE Sylvania Inc. and UAW, Local 1608, 1973; Publication (Box 498, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Contract between GTE Sylvania Inc. and UAW, Local 1608, 1976; Publication (Box 498, Folder 4)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 499, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Benefits Plans and Agreements -- UAW and the Ford Motor Company -- (Part II & III only), 1984; Publication (Box 499, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Agreements between Ford Motor Co. and UAW -- (Part I only), 1984; Publication (Box 499, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Supplemental Agreements covering Emoploye Stock ownership plan, 1984; Publication (Box 499, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Local agreements -- UAW/Local 664 General Motors, Assembly Div., Tarrytown, NY, 1984; Publication (Box 499, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Agreement between General Motors corp. and the UAW, 1987; Publication (Box 499, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 499, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Agreement covering Health Care Ins. Program -- Exhibit C and C-1 to agreement between General Motors Corp and UAW, 1984; Publication (Box 499, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Supplemental Agreement covering Health Care Ins. Program -- Exhibit C and C-1 to agreement between General Motors Corp and UAW, 1984; Publication (Box 499, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Suppplemental Agreement covering Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan -- Exhibit D to agreement between General Motors Corp and UAW, 1984; Publication (Box 499, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Suppplemental Agreement covering Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan -- Exhibit D to agreement between General Motors Corp and UAW, 1984; Publication (Box 499, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 499, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Agreement covering Pension Plan -- Exhibit A to agreement between General Motors and UAW, 1984; Publication (Box 499, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Supplemental Agreement covering Pension Plan -- Exhibit A to agreement between General Motors and UAW, 1984; Publication (Box 499, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Supplemental Agreement covering Group Life and Disability Ins. Program -- Exhibit B to agreement between General Motors and UAW, 1984; Publication (Box 499, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Supplemental Agreement covering Group Life and Disability Ins. Program -- Exhibit B to agreement between General Motors and UAW, 1984; Publication (Box 499, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Agreement between General Motors Corporation and the UAW: September 21, 1984 (Effective October 15, 1984), Publication (Box 499, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Summary - Major improvements and changes -- UAW-GM Benefit Plans under the 1979 Collective Bargaining Agreement, Publication (Box 499, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 500, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 1990 National Agreement and Supllemental Agreements between General Motors Corporation and the UAW: Miscellaneous documents, Publication (Box 500, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 500, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreement between General Motors Corporation and the UAW: October 8, 1987 (Effective October 26, 1987), Publication (Box 500, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Local agreements between Buick-Oldsmobile-Cadillac Group (BOC), General Motors Corporation, Lordstown Assembly Plant and Local 1112, United Autoworkers: October 14, 1986, (Effective November 17, 1986), Publication (Box 500, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Supplemental Agreement covering Life and Disability Benefits Program, Exhibity B to agreement between General Motors Corp. and UAW, 1987; Publication (Box 500, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Supplemental Agreement covering Pension Plan -- Exhibit A to agreement between General Motors and UAW, 1987; Publication (Box 500, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Supplemental Agreement covering Pension Plan -- Exhibit A to agreement between General Motors and UAW, 1987; Publication (Box 500, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 500, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Agreement covering Health Care Ins. Program -- Exhibit C and C-1 to agreement between General Motors Corp and UAW, 1987; Publication (Box 500, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Supplemental Agreement covering Health Care Ins. Program -- Exhibit C and C-1 to agreement between General Motors Corp and UAW, 1987; Publication (Box 500, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Supplemental Agreement covering UAW-GM Legal Service Plan -- Exhibit I to agreement between General Motors Corp. and UAW, 1987; Publication (Box 500, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Supplemental Agreement covering UAW-GM Legal Service Plan -- Exhibit I to agreement between General Motors Corp. and UAW, 1987; Publication (Box 500, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Supplemental Agreement covering Life and Disability Benefits Program, Exhibity B to agreement between General Motors Corp. and UAW, 1987; Publication (Box 500, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Supplemental Agreement covering Personal Savings Plan -- Exhibit G to agreement between General Motors Corp. and UAW, 1987; Publication (Box 500, Folder 3)